[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What cruel punishment did Vlad III, Prince of Wallachia, who inspired Bram Stokers 1897 novel Dracula, like to impose?", "correct_answer": "Impalement", "incorrect_answers": ["Skinning alive", "Burning alive", "Blood draining"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Pendleton Civil Service Reform Act, which established the United States Civil Service Commission, was drafted during the office of which President?", "correct_answer": "Chester A. Arthur", "incorrect_answers": ["Theodore Roosevelt", "Abraham Lincoln", "Williaam Howard Taft"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from The World Is Not Enough double-crosses Elektra King?", "correct_answer": "Davidov", "incorrect_answers": ["Fomashen", "Kyrialevski", "Ubrolin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You can make your risotto even more delicious by stirring a quarter cup of heavy cream, which would turn your Risotto into this kind.", "correct_answer": "Mantecato", "incorrect_answers": ["A la Romana", "Risotto allo Champagne", "Vialone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Potemkin Villages were fake settlements, erected at the direction of Russian minister Grigori Potemkin, to impress which monarch?", "correct_answer": "Catherine the Great", "incorrect_answers": ["Louis XIV", "Peter the Great", "Louis XVI"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a section of the famous Niagara Falls?", "correct_answer": "Horseshoe Falls", "incorrect_answers": ["Horseback Falls", "Horsetail Falls", "Horseman Falls"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1955, Doc Brown, one of the lead characters in Back to the Future lives on which street?", "correct_answer": "Riverside Drive", "incorrect_answers": ["Maplewood Ave", "John F. Kennedy Drive", "Pine St"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these books was not  written by Steve Allen?", "correct_answer": "Murder in the Valley", "incorrect_answers": ["The Murder Game", "Murder in Manhattan", "The Talk Show Murders"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did Christopher Reeve become paralyzed?", "correct_answer": "He had a horseback riding accident", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "He had a car accident", "He had a flying accident"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is NOT a state capital?", "correct_answer": "Dallas", "incorrect_answers": ["Dover", "Des Moines", "Denver"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom, what two objects are Indiana Jones and Willie trying to get while the panicked crowd in the nightclub kick them around?", "correct_answer": "a diamond and a tube of poison antidote", "incorrect_answers": ["A sacred relic and a diamond", "a map and a diamond", "a gun and a ruby"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All birds are descendants of dinosaurs.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]